你好啊
How you doing?
我是菲尔·邓菲
Phil Dunphy.
我要如何才能让你张口问
What do I have to do to get you to ask
"我要如何才能让你看上这辆车"
"What do I have to do to get you into this car today?"
要不 我们先来个试驾你看怎么样
Well, why don't we start it with a test drive?
我去拿钥匙
I'll get the keys.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
正合我意啊
Right where I want him.
快过来 瞅瞅这个
Come here. Come look at this.
一旦你偏离行车道 这玩意儿就会提醒你
This thing warns you if you deviate from your lane.
我的车 我老婆也具有相同功能
In my car, that's my wife.
"安德瑞 你要是拿我生命冒险
"Andre, if you try to kill me,
老娘就先收了你"
I swear I will kill you!"
我想接下来陪伴我39个月的就会是这辆车了
Well, I guess this is what I'll be driving for the next 39 months.
休怪我观察力太明锐
This is my D.N.A. talking,
但你似乎并没有很兴奋满足
But you do not seem sufficiently excited
这可是一辆全新的凯迪拉克啊
about the prospect of driving a new Cadillac.
没 我兴奋得很 只是一直都是老一套
No, it's great. I've just leased the same thing forever.
但内心深处其实想弄点刺激的
Part of me wants to shake things up.
我也说不清
I don't know.
比如换一个...
Get something like...
那样的
Like that.
克里克上校风范 赞啊
Colonel Klink, that is nice.
我们第一次带着莉莉坐城铁
We took Lily on her first train ride.
去唐人街的短途路程
Just a quick trip to chinatown.
原本还担心她会误以为
I was worried she would think
我们要把她送回越南
We were taking her back to Vietnam,
不过她表现还好
But she seemed okay.
可不是嘛
Yeah, yeah.
可能因为她离开越南时还只是个婴儿吧
Possibly because she was an infant when she left vietnam.
其次 越南和中国是两码事
Also, Vietnam is not China.
不过 我带上根棒棒糖以防万一
Well, I had a lollipop with me just in case.
我真开心我们能这么做
I love that we're doing this.
慢慢涉足她生活的城市对她很重要
It's important for her to explore the city she lives in.
真是鱼龙混杂啊
So much diversity.
快把钱包放你前面的口袋里
Keep your wallet in your front pocket.
我的鞋带散了
My shoe's untied.
小乖乖 是哦 来 先坐下
Oh, sweetie, it is. Here, have a seat.
就这里 好样的 小兔兔拿好
Right here. There you go. Hey, hold bunny.
-不 不 不 不 -小兔兔
- No! No, no, no, no, no, no! - Bunny!
你怎么就没接住呢 米奇尔
How did you miss that, Mitchell?
列车长 我...
Mr. Conductor! I-I...
那什么
What?
我在给手消毒呢
I was purell-ing!
我不就这样嘛 你干嘛突然扔过来
And it's me! Why would you toss it?
我手忙不过来了这理由充分吗
Because my hands were full?
还我小兔兔
I want bunny!
知道 好的 我有个主意
I know. W--okay, I have an idea.
我们赶下一班城铁 然后去追前面那班
Let's catch the next train and ride it till it catches up.
城铁是追不上的 追上了那叫追尾
They don't catch up. That's called a collision.
那行你说 你想一个更好的办法呢
Okay, well, do you have a better idea?
-就是你弄丢的 -不 是你扔丢的
- You're the one that lost it. - No, you tossed it.
扔的人才是弄丢的人
He who tossed it lost it.
别为了推卸责任跟我耍嘴皮子
Don't try to clever your way out of this.
爸爸弄丢了兔兔
Daddy lost bunny.
她说的是你
She means you.
自打小时候我就梦想着能有这么一辆车
Oh, I wanted a car like this since I was a kid.
我也是
Me, too.
我曾想象着那风掠过我的发梢
I used to imagine the wind blowing through my perm,
再配上霍尔与奥兹的歌
blasting some Hall & Oates,
和我的麦克疯先生一起逍遥自在
maybe horsing around with my Mr. Microphone...
得了 那会儿咱俩还没那么熟
Yeah, we wouldn't have been friends back then.
心动不如行动啊
You should buy it.
不 这太不切实际了
No, it's not practical.
实际 你见过人临死之前躺床上
Practical? You never see a person on their deathbed
说 "我要是在活得在实际点就好了"
saying, "I wish I'd have been more practical."
临死之人的肺腑之言我见得多了 菲尔
I see a lot of people on their deathbed, Phil.
多了去了
A lot.
你手下的病人都是胳膊腿伤 不至于辞世吧
I thought you operated on knees and elbows.
菲尔 这车真的不错
Phil, this is a nice car.
价格也只有新车的一半而已
And it's half the price of a new car.
你要是不买 我就上了
If you don't buy it, I will.
克莱尔知道可怎么办
What would Claire say?
那好吧 我们去找那种特殊构造的车
You know what? Maybe we should find you
那种可以让你挺直腰杆的车
Something with a little more lumbar support.
知道吗 你要是自己连个主心骨都没有
Yeah. You know, with you not having a spine and all.
-我有主心骨 -你确定你有主心骨吗
- I have a spine. - Do you have a spine?
-我有主心骨 -要去兜风测测性能吗
- I have a spine. - So wanna take it for a spin?
这样吧 我更想测测她的"性能"
You know what? I'd rather take her for a spin.
赶紧把她放平整利索了
Let's get her top down
看看她"性能"如何
and see what she can do.
我... 我说的是那敞篷车
I'm--no, I meant the convertible.
我刚跟那大堂经理聊了下
Well, I just talked to the concierge,
客房服务能帮我留一块面包布丁
and room service will save me a bread pudding.
那我总算放心了
Load off my mind.
尽管嘲笑我 不过《旅游与休闲》杂志
You mock me, but "Travel and leisure"
可说了那是不能错过的美食
Says it's not to be missed.
这周末 我们一家要去卵石滩[加州]
This weekend, we're going up to pebble beach.
去会会那群高中的橄榄球队友们
I'm gonna meet a bunch of guys I played high school football with.
天啊 那段岁月可真是难忘
Man, those were the good old days.
是啊 但当年你要是女人或者
Yeah, unless you were a woman,
黑人 西裔 同性恋那日子就糟糕了
black, hispanic, or gay.
没错 不过你要是一个白种的直男
True, but if you were a straight white guy
还打橄榄球
who played football,
每一天都是快乐的好日子
you really couldn't have a bad day.
歌洛莉亚
Gloria?
我该戴哪块表
Which watch should I pack?
这块霸气外漏 这款价值连城
This one's showier. This one's more expensive.
就一块表而已你干嘛那么在乎
Why do you care so much about a watch?
我要怎么跟你说才不会显得太臭屁呢
How do I say this without sounding like an ass?
那帮人可当我是个传奇人物
I'm kind of a legend to these guys.
这么说不行
Not like that.
瞧瞧酷爹风范
Who's your daddy?
哇哦 这车是谁的啊
Whoa! Whose car is this?
-我的 -我说服他买的
- Mine! - I talked him into it.
真的吗 买这车老妈没意见吗
Seriously? Mom's gonna let you have this?
卢克 卢克 卢克...
Luke, Luke, Luke...
你妈人呢
Where is she?
老爸 我觉得这样不好
Dad, I don't like this.
为什么
Why not?
我朋友茉莉她爸就买了辆跑车
My friend Molly's dad bought a sports car,
现在他住在一个单间公寓里
and now he lives in a studio apartment
跟一个在"永驻21岁"上班的姑娘约会
and dates a girl who works at Forever 21,
那姑娘可两年后才到21岁
which she won't be for two years.
听到没
Hear that?
宝贝们 我不会抛下你们母亲的
Honey, I'm not leaving your mom.
或许还真由不得你
Might not be your call.
我的天啊 这车太炫了
Oh, my god, it's so pretty!
我爱死它了 也爱死你了
I love it! And I love you,
我答应你 一定格外小心地驾驶它
and I promise I'll take super good care of it!
能让我来说吗
Can I tell her?
求你了 我要求的事并不多
Please. I ask for so little.
艾丽克斯 姐妹俩要和睦
Alex, be nice to your sister.
这是老爸的车 不是你的
It's dad's car, not yours.
说什么 年老的你和这新潮的车不搭啊
What? But you're too old for this!
就跟去年一个样
It's just like last year
你死也不愿意脱下那些紧身牛仔裤
when you wouldn't take off those skinny jeans.
不愿脱 还是 没法脱
Wouldn't or couldn't?
我穿着可性感呢
Hey. I looked hot.
你配上这车也一样性感
And you look hot in this car.
让我来告诉你们一些你们老爸的事儿
Let me tell you something about your dad.
你们的爸爸是个目标明确的人
Your dad is a man who knows what he wants,
而且说到做到
and he gets it.
反正我是这么听说的
At least that's what I heard.
你们懂的 当局者迷 朋观者清嘛
You know, I was there more as a friend and an observer than anything.
-安德瑞 -你好 克莱尔
- Andre. - Hey, Claire.
亲爱的 这是你买的新车吗
Honey. Is this the new car?
我知道看起来不实用
I know it looks impractical,
不过安德瑞跟我说了好些临死之人的事
but Andre's seen a lot of people die.
我没有不高兴
I'm not upset.
没生气 这车挺漂亮
I'm not upset. It's a beautiful car.
就是惊讶你没买辆大车 仅此而已
Just surprised you didn't get the sedan, that's all.
不错
Beautiful.
见到你很高兴 克莱...
Good seeing, you, Cl--
真的很漂亮
Mm. It's beautiful.
刚刚是怎么回事
What just happened?
她眼都没眨一下
She did not blink once.
进去坐一会儿吧
Do you wanna come in for a minute?
不了 我得 你知道 找我老婆去
No, I gotta... You know, I gotta get to the wife.
你要不要
Well, do you...
-要不要我送你一程 -不用 不用
- Uh, do you need a ride or anything? - No. No, no,
我打算 跑回去
I'm gonna, uh, I'm-a jog.
-你干嘛跑啊 -我跑步回去就行了
- Why--why are you running? - I'm just gonna jog!
莉莉没了兔兔 一晚上没合眼
Lily was up all night because she didn't have bunny,
我们也跟着不能睡
which means that we were up all night
因为她的兔兔没了
because she didn't have bunny.
天呐 她肯定哭了有
God, she must have cried for...
多久来着 小卡
How long was it, Cam?
小卡 小卡
Cam. Cam.
不好意思
Oh, sorry.
昨晚上太混乱了 因为莉莉的
Uh, last night was rough because Lily...
-说过了 -兔兔不见了
- Covered it. - didn't have bunny.
杰 说啊 我们到跑道上来干嘛
Jay, tell me, why are we on the runway?
大惊喜 我们要乘私人飞机去
Surprise! We're taking a private plane.
我还从没坐过私人飞机呢
Wow! I've never been on a private plane!
以后也别想坐
And you never will.
我不会上那个小玩意儿的
I am not getting on that little thing!
要是皮筋断了 我们掉下来怎么办
What if the rubber band snaps and we fall out of the sky?
安全系数很高的 人家是正规航空公司
It's perfectly safe. It's a legitimate airline!
你们好
Hey, folks.
怎么有三个人
Whoa. Nobody said three.
好吧 起飞前
All right. Before we take off,
我得登记一下各位的体重
I'm gonna need to get everyone's weight here.
-没问题 我有190磅 -好的
- No problem. I'm about 190. - Okay.
那样的话 我275磅
Oh, yeah. In that case, I'm 275.
歌洛莉亚 我不会让你和曼尼有危险的
Gloria, I would never put you and Manny in danger.
走吧 相信我这一回
Now come on! Trust me on this!
太棒了
Beautiful.
这一路都得听美国音乐
It's American music the whole way,
谁也别说话
and I don't wanna hear a word.
-怎么样了 跑车男 -棒极了
- How you doing there, sport? - Great. Yeah.
帅呆了 你知道帅在哪儿吗
Awesome. You know what's awesome?
这辆车的发动机在后备箱里
Is this car has the engine in the trunk,
这就意味着我得...
so that means I get to...
把这些展板放在座位上 真酷
Put these signs in the seat, which is cool.
是相当酷
Very cool.
怎么了
What?
没什么 客户想让我
Oh, nothing. My, uh, client just wants me
载她一起过去看房
to pick her up on the way to the open house,
没问题 我只要把展板拿下来
which is great. I'll, uh, drop the sign off
然后穿过镇子
and just swing across town to...
她还要带上她妈妈和设计师
Oh. She's bringing her mom and a designer.
说不定后备箱坐得下
Well, maybe they'll fit in the trunk.
就知道你会撒气
Here it comes!
哪里 我开玩笑的
What? I was making a joke.
小女子 你耍的什么把戏
What's your game, woman?
没什么 你是成年人 能自己做主
I have no game. You're an adult. You can make your own choices.
我什么时候有这待遇了
Since when?
你想借用这面包车吗
Do you wanna borrow the minivan?
对 求求你了
Yes, please.
行 那你去接孩子放学
Okay, fine. Then you're gonna have to pick up the kids from school.
好吧 我投降
Okay, I can't take it.
你想说什么 尽管往我这儿招呼吧
If you got something to say, just say it.
我无话可说
I have nothing to say.
-不言自明了 -随你怎么想吧
- That just says it all. - Well...Ok.
行 好 谢了 塞丽娜
All--all right. Thank you, Serena.
晚上见
See you tonight.
好消息 他们帮我把按摩时间调早上了
Good news--they rescheduled my massage for the morning.
坏消息是按摩师换成男的了
Bad news--it's a dude.
别怪我 要怪怪你妈
Don't blame me. It's your mom's fault.
你知道有多少人因为乘这种飞机丧命了吗
Do you know how many people have died in these planes?
约翰·丹沃
John Denver,
佩茜·克琳
Patsy Cline,
里奇·瓦伦斯
Ritchie Valens.
就你那破锣嗓 我保你没事
I've heard you sing. I think you're safe.
行了 听着
All right, look,
欢迎晚宴四小时后开始
The welcome dinner starts in four hours.
我们开到那儿要五个小时
It's a 5-hour drive.
路上没时间上厕所了
No bathroom breaks.
所以我劝你还是少喝点儿
Yeah, I think you're gonna want to hold on to that cup.
糟糕
Damn it!
-怎么回事 -一个大坑
- What was that? - Giant pothole.
撞得火花四溅了都
The dash is lighting up like a christmas tree.
轮胎破了
Tire's blown!
要是在天上就不会有这种事了
This never would have happened if we were in the air!
要是天上发生这种事 我们就没活路了
If this had happened in the air, we wouldn't be in the air.
我们就上天堂唱摇滚了
We would be in rock 'n' roll heaven!
你觉得怎么样
Okay, what do you think?
我打算把这些贴到地铁里去
I'm gonna put these in the subway.
这张看起来好像是莉莉丢了
Okay, it looks like, uh, Lily's missing
然后我们悬赏25美元把她找回来
and we're offering $25 to get her back.
荒唐 正常的人怎么会...
Oh, don't be ridiculous. No one in their right mind--
好吧 现在我也这么觉得了
Okay. That's all I see now.
-这张呢 -我看看
- How about this one? - Okay. Um...
毛绒兔子失踪 毛色灰白相间
"Missing--stuffed bunny. Brown and white fur.
富有同情心的眼神 解释一下这句
Sympathetic eyes." What are sympathetic eyes?
反正不是你那样
Not those.
我只是 没法接受
I just--I don't really love the idea
把我们的电话号码贴得地铁里到处都是
of our phone number being up in the subway.
行 那我们换个方式
Okay, let's play a different game.
我来提问 你来解决 如何
How about I be the problem, and you be the solution?
对不起 我不应该吹毛求疵的
I'm sorry. I shouldn't be so critical.
我知道你不过是想 有了
I know you're just trying to--got it!
突然想到一个好主意
Just came up with a better idea.
花了我五秒钟不到
Took me less than five seconds.
我看看
Okay...
我听不见 什么
I can't hear you. What?
窗玻璃摇下来
Window.
我不会弄
I don't know...
我按了什么
Gah! What did I do?
天呐
Oh. Oh, my.
-你好 -你好 车不错
- Yes. Hi. - Hey, nice car.
谢谢
Thank you.
你是去海边吗 还是
You gonna drive up the coast, or...
不是 就是去办点事
Oh, no. I'm gonna do some errands, actually.
有些人可能会去买辆离谱的车
Yeah, 'cause other people might go and buy a crazy car
发动机还在后备箱里 我可不会
with an engine in the-- in the trunk, but not me.
不 我是个负责任的人
No. I'm responsible. Mm-hmm.
我们有三个孩子 这车怎么坐得下
We have three kids. You can't pick up three kids in this car.
根本坐不下
You can't.
你 这个
You--it... It...
我会追上你的 来了
I'll get you... Catch ya.
走了
I'm going!
也许我确实有那么一点点搓火
Maybe I was a teeny bit mad.
于是我抛开琐事 驶向大海
So I blew off my errands and headed up the coast.
是时候让我潇洒走一回了
It was my turn to be irresponsible.
幸好 我包包里还有墨镜
And luckily, I had sunscreen in my purse.
你的车架坏了
Well, your strut's shot,
更换的零件要过一天才能到
And we can't get parts for at least a day.
这下好了
Fantastic.
依我看
I don't suppose
你们这儿也没租车的地方吧
there's any place you can rent cars anywhere around here?
先生 这小镇没你想象的那么落后
Know what, sir? We're not some one-horse town.
当然能租到车
Of course you can rent a car.
只是不巧都租完了
It just happens to be out for the day.
难以置信
Unbelievable.
-整个周末都泡汤了 -很抱歉 杰
- We're gonna miss the whole weekend. - I am sorry, Jay.
我知道他们把你看得有多重要
I know how much you mean to those guys,
也知道他们有多想见你
and I know how much they want to see you.
真是不好意思
I'm so sorry.
容我说一句
Uh, excuse me.
你真的是
You are...
太漂亮了
so pretty.
如果你们真的必须要去哪儿
And if you really need to get somewhere,
或许我能帮上忙
maybe I can help you out.
好啊 拜托了 谢谢 怎样都行
Ay, yes, please! Thank you! Anything!
瞧瞧 我私藏的宝贝
Check it out. Restored it myself.
不行
No.
我才不在这小机场里上这架小飞机
I did not get in the little plane at the little airport!
死也不坐这个...
I'm not gonna get in this...
开飞机的还是那个连车都修不好的家伙
flown by that guy that couldn't fix our car!
歌洛莉亚 要么就坐这个
Gloria, it's either this,
要么只好住旅馆了
or we're in the motel.
现在这情况可不怎么乐观
I don't like the sound of that.
宾馆变成旅馆 档次立马跟着下跌
A lot of amenities disappear when an "H" Becomes an "M."
话说 我刚认识你那会儿
You know, when I met you,
你还从桶里扒麦片吃呢
you were eating cereal out of a bucket.
嘿 莉莉 你猜怎么着
Hey, Lily, guess what?
什么事
What?
兔兔给我们传信了
Uh, we just heard from Bunny.
这办法糟透了
This is a terrible idea.
不 这办法好极了
No, it's fantastic.
兔兔说 他正在经历一场华丽的冒险
Bunny said he's on an amazing adventure
并且特别享受那种生活
having the time of his life,
还说 你应该选一个他的好朋友
And that you should pick one of his best friends
在他外出的这段时间陪你入眠
to sleep with while he's gone.
兔兔不会说话
Bunny doesn't talk.
进行得"真"顺利
This is going great.
他现在会说了 因为
He does now, because--
因为他上语文课了
because he took talking lessons.
那你想选哪一个呢
So what do you think, huh?
小海龟 还是长颈鹿
Turtle or giraffe
还是 小驯鹿呢
or, uh, little reindeer?
兔兔现在在哪儿
Where's bunny now?
在圣路易斯
Uh, St. Louis.
为什么
Why?
他去看他女朋友了
He's visiting his girlfriend.
他没有女朋友
He doesn't have a girlfriend.
他有个男朋友
He has a boyfriend!
还我兔兔
I want bunny!
好吧 等等 莉莉
Okay. No, no, Lily.
莉莉 要不选泰迪熊吧
Lily, uh, what about miss, uh, Teddy bear?
不好吗 那老虎博士呢 也不好吗
Huh? No? Uh, Dr. Tiger? No?
鱼先生呢
Mr. Fish?
我要兔兔 我要去圣路易斯
I want bunny. I'm going to St. Louis.
不是吧 这鱼叫"尼莫"都不知道
Really? You don't know Nemo?
屋里可都是循环播放着的
It's on an endless loop in the den.
我可没那闲工夫
I have a job.
然后博迪传球给我
And then Bodie kicked it to me,
我带球过了迈克 传给了泰勒
and I dribbled it past Michael and got it to Tyler...
开不上崭新的靓车 我很不爽
I was bummed not to be in my new cool car,
所以我没有像平时一样跟孩子们嬉闹
so I wasn't joking around with the kids like I usually do.
要不是被那小子绊倒 我就射门得分了
And I would've scored if that kid didn't trip me.
裁判居然没看到
I can't believe the ref didn't see it.
奥利维亚肯定看到了
I bet Olivia saw it.
你踢球时 她总是盯着你
She's always watching you when you play.
是啊 我知道 似乎她很喜欢足球
Yeah, I know. It's like she's in love with soccer.
唉 别再给我发短信了
Ugh. Stop texting me!
怎么了
What?
是科瑞 他太黏人了
Corey. He is so clingy.
但是 开车接送孩子还是有好处的
But, you know, there's something about driving your kids around.
你在前排 他们在后排
You're in the front, they're in the back.
他们忘记你在那儿
They forget you're there,
于是你知道了许多小秘密
and you learn so much.
感觉我像《雾中猩猩》里的西格妮·韦弗
You're like sigourney weaver in "Gorillas in the mist."
不过猩猩的咀嚼声比较小
Except gorillas make less noise chewing.
一开上沿海公路 我就一路狂飙
Once I hit the coast highway, I didn't stop.
关掉了手机
I turned off my cell phone.
午饭吃了鱼肉卷 真是太疯狂了
I ate fish tacos for lunch. It was insane!
好多年都没这种自由的感觉了
I haven't felt that free in years.
压力一下子就不见踪影了
All my stress completely disappeared...
车钥匙也一并没了
And so did my keys.
抱歉 但这些标志真是傻到家了
I'm sorry, but... These signs are ridiculous.
你说得对 我应该用赫维提卡字体
Oh, you're right. I should have used helvetica.
那样更符合我们目前火烧眉毛的状况
It much better represents the urgency of our situation.
不 我是说咱费尽心思就为找个娃娃
No, the lengths that we're going to for a stuffed animal.
小卡 该让莉莉体会什么是"失去"了
You know, cam, maybe it's time lily learned about loss.
不 她才3岁 我最懂了
No, she's 3, and I know.
你知道吗 在农场时
Do you know how many times
我不得不无数次和动物朋友们告别
I had to say good-bye to a furry friend on the farm?
你不正因此变得更坚强[肥壮]了吗
And didn't it make you stronger?
没错 那时我正在长身体
Yeah, because I was a growing boy
而动物肉富含了蛋白质 高营养
and they were chock-full of protein.
但那依然会让我心碎
But it was still heartbreaking.
那可以塑造人的品质
It builds character.
我小时候 有一回
You know, once, when I was a kid,
我爸把我的卢克·天行者玩偶遗失在机场
my dad left my Luke Skywalker doll on an airplane,
-我特别气 -等会儿 哪一款卢克
- and I was so angry-- - Wait, which--which Luke?
穿短袍的 还是黑衣的
Shorty robe or dress blacks?
-穿短袍的 -天呐
- Shorty robe. - Oh, my.
你知道他怎么找回它吗
And you know what he did to get it back?
他什么都没干 什么都没
Not a damn thing. Nope.
他连动动手指头去打个电话都没有
He didn't lift one pudgy finger to make a single phone call,
而我挺过来了
and I got over it.
是啊 我希望你和莉莉
Yeah, well, I want you and Lily
能有健康的父女关系
to have the same healthy relationship
就像你和你爹那样 必须的
you and your father have. For sure.
好吧 把传单给我
All right, give me these flyers.
我把它们发给这些流浪汉
I'm gonna take everything to this side of the homeless guy.
米奇尔
Mitchell!
我错了 我们该怎么称呼他们呢
Sorry, what are we supposed to say now
无家可归的人 还是啥
Home-challenged? Or...
不 快看
No, look!
天呐 是兔兔
Oh, my god! It's bunny!
莉莉会高兴坏了的
Oh, Lily's gonna be so happy.
真是太好了 快去拿回来
Oh, that's so great. Go ahead and get it.
-啥 我去 -对啊
- What, me? - Yeah.
干嘛让我去拿回来
Why should I go and get it?
我才不会去呢
Well, I-I'm not gonna do it.
为什么 是我发现的
Why? I spotted it.
你离得近
You're closer.
这是你的使命 想想"卢克·天行者"
It's your journey. Luke Skywalker?
想想"超越自我" 想想你爹 快去
Pattern-breaking? Your father? Get in there.
好吧
Fine.
嗨 先生
Sir--hi, sir.
你好 你 你
Hello, you--you...
你好
Hello.
你好 先生
He-hello? Sir...
-我不能 -我的老天爷啊
- I-I can't... - Oh, for god sakes!
-她要恨咱就恨吧 -你心中有恨也照样成才了
- Let her hate us. - You turned out great.
-的确啊 不是吗 -你是个大律师呢
- I did, didn't I? - You're a big lawyer.
我预想中的按摩可不是这样的
This is not the massage I had in mind.
好的
All right.
这样
Okay.
大约一小时后 有辆火车会经过这儿
In about an hour, a train goes through town
可以把我们带到卵石滩那儿
that will get us close to pebble beach.
严格意义上说 那不是一辆客运火车
Now it's not technically a-a passenger train,
-所以不会停站 -什么
- so it won't be stopping. - What?
我们到时候得跑快点
So we gotta get running real good.
高跟鞋就算了吧 还有带上那毛毯
No high-heeled shoes. And it wouldn't be wrong
应该也能派上用场了吧
if we took that blanket with us, either, huh?
你们觉得如何 来一场流浪大冒险如何
So what do you say? Anybody up for a hobo adventure?
真要投票的话 我反对
If we're voting, I'm a "No".
曼尼 我们出去一会儿就回来
Manny, we're gonna be right back.
我们去停车场那个机器里弄点冰块回来
We're gonna get some ice from the machine in the parking lot.
够上档次
Classy.
杰 这是要闹哪样 有意思吗
Jay, this is getting crazy. Is it worth it?
我就想会会三五老友而已
I wanna see the old gang.
你是真心想见他们 还是单纯想去炫耀
Do you wanna see them or you want to show off to them?
私人飞机啊 名贵手表啊
The private plane, the fancy watch.
你只是想回味
You still want to feel
自己在大学里当大佬的滋味吧
that you're the big kahuna on the campus.
才没有呢 我压根没往那方面想
That's not it. That's not even a thing.
算了 我要带曼尼回家了
You know what? I'm taking Manny home.
如果你执意要去坐那什么...
If you want to go in the takka-takka-takka-takka,
成 你就一个人去吧
okay, go to pebble beach by yourself.
不要 说什么呢 计划不是这样的
No, what? That's not the plan.
如果你那么想去
If you wanna go there so bad,
这就是唯一的办法了
that's the only way you're gonna get there.
不是我自己想要去那儿
I'm not trying to get me there.
我是想带你去那儿
I'm trying to get you there!
-什么 -听着
- What? - Look...
关于当大佬的事 我有点言过其实
I may have exaggerated the size... kahuna I was.
我可能
I may not...
严格意义上来说 都没当过大佬
technically have been a kahuna.
我那时很怯懦 大多时间我都是
I was shy, and I spent most of my time...
坐冷板凳
on the bench.
可你一直说得好像自己当时很...
But you always made it sound like you--
我知道自己吹成什么样
Oh, I know what I made it sound like.
人们都觉得我不会有大出息
People didn't expect much from me,
还有
and, um...
他们肯定没想到
they certainly didn't expect me
我能娶到你这样的美人
to end up with... somebody like you.
所以你只是把我当个
So this is all about you
战利品带过去炫耀是吗
parading me around like a trophy?
没错
Yes.
你干嘛早不讲
Why didn't you say so?
扮花瓶我可最在行
I can be a trophy!
好啦 赶紧把这个尤物带去卵石滩吧
Come on. We need to get this up to pebble beach.
曼尼 出发啦 快收拾一下
Manny! We're leaving! Get ready!
太棒了 我们十分钟内离开的话
Oh, good. If we get out of here in the next ten minutes,
就只用付一个小时的房费
we don't have to pay for the second hour.
玩得怎么样啊 开跑车的
How you doing there, sport?
-真抱歉 -没事啦
- I'm sorry. - That's okay.
多谢
Thanks.
那
So...
跑这么远来做什么
Whatcha doing all the way up here?
是不是生气啦
Did someone snap?
没错 有一点
A little. Yeah.
就因为你买那辆破跑车
I was mad at you for buying that stupid sports car.
我就知道
I knew it!
但我错了
And I was wrong.
这车太棒了 一整天都棒极了
It's a great car. God, I had the best day.
菲尔 我还做了侧手翻
Phil, I did cartwheels.
不带我吗
Without me?
对
Yeah.
你知道有小姑娘喜欢上咱家卢克了吗
Hey, did you know there's a girl with a crush on Luke?
-奥利维亚吧 -对
- Olivia. - Yeah.
海莉跟科瑞彻底玩完了
Oh, and Haley's totally done with Corey.
那倒算新闻
That's new.
艾丽克斯在自学汉语
Alex is teaching herself Chinese
等回头中国把咱全部收购后可以派上用场
so she'll be useful when they finish buying us.
她就是个怪小孩
She's so weird.
我真的很想驾车带孩子们四处逛逛
I really want to be able to drive the kids around.
我本该买个大点的车上班用 是我错了
I need a bigger car for work. I made a mistake.
你没犯错 你买它是有原因的
No, you didn't. You bought it for a reason.
为什么咱们后来就不到海边来了
When did we stop coming to the beach?
好像是从艾丽克斯
I think it was when Alex
绘制水质报告开始的
started printing out water quality reports.
以后该头痛的就是中国了
She'll be China's problem soon.
你知道吗
You know...
我们并不需要跑车才能来这儿
We don't need a sports car to get out here.
我们许下个约定好了
We should just make a pact.
每月找个机会 逃离尘嚣奔向大海
Once a month, we get out to the beach.
别人问起 就说出来办点事儿
And we tell everyone we're running errands.
-好的 -好的
- Yeah. - Yeah.
那干洗店你还没去是吗
So you didn't get to the dry cleaner?
世人常说 生命中最重要的事
They say the important thing in life
并非抵达终点
isn't the destination.
而是旅途本身
It's the journey,
是一路上遇到的重重挑战
the challenges you face along the way...
是出乎意料的峰回路转
the unexpected twists and turns...
是被你击溃的失望与沮丧
the disappointments you overcome.
看看我从网上买到什么了
Look what I found on the internet.
我的天啊 是穿着短袍的卢克·天行者
Oh, my god! It's Luke Skywalker in his shorty robe!
-我好喜欢 小卡 -是我的
- I love it, Cam---. - Mine!
但世人皆错
But they're wrong.
终点才最重要
It's all about the destination,
尤其是当终点是
especially when the destination
有超棒海景的酒店时
is your amazing oceanfront hotel.
再次感谢你 塞丽娜
Thank you again, Serena.
最诚挚的问候 曼尼·迪尔加多
Warmest regards, Manny Delgado.
这孩子干嘛呢
What's he doing?
他给那大堂经理送花呢
He's sending flowers to the concierge.
-不是吧 -喂
- Oh, jeez. - Hey...
信用卡号
Credit card.
你老婆让你改主意了 对吧
She wore you down, didn't she?
跟克莱尔一点关系都没有
This is not about Claire.
是我自己真心想把车卖给你
I really want to sell you the car.
真悲哀 你居然被女人制服了
It's sad. She got you to believe that.
不是 我
No, I...
我只是发现敞篷跑车不适合自己
Turns out I'm just not a convertible guy.
好吧 你的便宜我来占
Well, your loss is my gain.
-这车多神气啊 菲尔 -对吧
- It's a sweet ride, Phil. - Right?
必须是
It really is.
-不对 -咋了
- Uh-oh. - What?
我好像闻到一股霉味儿
I'm getting, like, a whiff of mildew.
没闻到啊
I don't smell anything.
没错 就是霉味
Yep. That's mildew.
这车肯定被水泡过
This car's been in the flood.
是卡特里娜飓风受灾车
It's a Katrina car!
居然把受灾车卖我 气死我了 菲尔
I'm offended that you tried to sell me a Katrina car, Phil!
你老婆不准你买敞篷车 是不是
Your wife won't let you have a convertible, will she?
我哪知道 因为我都没胆去问
We will never know, 'cause I'm afraid to ask.
再见了 菲尔
See you later, Phil.
怎么每次谈到老婆就跑
Why you running again?